Guide to the James Harvey Rogers Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Index to Selected Correspondents
  - Rogers, James Harvey (1886-1939)
    - MacIver, Robert Morrison (1882-)
      - 9 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, New York
        - 1933 January 18 (Box 11)
        - 1933 January 20 (Box 11)
        - 1933 January 21 (Box 11)
        - 1933 March 1 (Box 11)
        - 1933 March 6 (Box 11)
        - 1933 March 7 (Box 11)
        - 1933 October 21 (Box 12)
        - 1934 January 17 (Box 13)
        - 1934 September 21 (Box 15)
    - Meyer, Eugene (1875-1959)
      - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
        - 1931 September 22 (Box 9)
        - 1933 March 4 (Box 11)
    - Millikan, Max Franklin (1913-)
      - 9 TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1935 July 25 (Box 17)
        - 1935 July 29 (Box 17)
        - 1935 August 21 (Box 17)
        - 1935 November 26 (Box 17)
        - 1936 January 13 (Box 17)
        - 1936 February 2 (Box 18)
        - 1936 April 21 (Box 18)
        - 1936 July 1 (Box 19)
        - 1939 April 20 (Box 24)
    - Mitchell, Wesley Clair (1874-1948)
      - 14 TLS and TL copy to James Harvey Rogers, New York
        - 1921 November 14 (Box 1)
        - 1924 May 5 (Box 2)
        - 1924 May 15 (Box 2)
        - 1926 October 20 (Box 3)
        - 1928 February 16 (Box 5)
        - 1928 March 24 (Box 5)
        - 1928 March 31 (Box 5)
        - 1928 November 19 (Box 5)
        - 1929 February 13 (Box 6)
        - 1929 March 11 (Box 6)
        - 1930 November 28 (Box 7)
        - 1931 January 27 (Box 8)
        - 1931 January 31 (Box 8)
        - 1931 April 9 (Box 8)
    - Morgenthau, Henry (1891-1963)
      - 10 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1933 December 8 (Box 13)
        - 1934 March 10 (Box 13)
        - 1934 October 1 (2) (Box 15)
        - 1934 October 9 (Box 15)
        - 1934 November 19 (Box 15)
        - 1935 February 4 (Box 16)
        - 1935 February 21 (Box 16)
        - 1936 September 29 (Box 19)
        - 1938 September 27 (Box 23)
    - Murphy, Louis T. (1876-1936). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Dubuque, Iowa, 1933 January 18 (Box 11)
    - Nelson, William Lester (1875-1946). TLS to James Harvey Rogets, Washington, D.C., 1930 May 7 (Box 7)
    - Noble, S. Randolph (1887-)
      - 8 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Montreal
        - 1931 June 27 (Box 8)
        - 1931 September 25 (Box 9)
        - 1932 February 20 (Box 10)
        - 1934 October 14 (Box 15)
        - 1935 December 27 (Box 17)
        - 1936 November 20 (Box 19)
        - 1936 December 8 (Box 20)
        - 1936 December 29 (Box 20)
    - Oburn, William Fielding (1886-1959)
      - 7 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1929 March 6 (Box 6)
        - 1929 March 28 (Box 6)
        - 1929 June 4 (Box 6)
        - 1932 January 4 (Box 9)
        - 1932 March 30 (Box 10)
        - 1932 April 15 (Box 10)
        - 1934 January 6 (Box 13)
    - Oliphant, Herman (1884-1939)
      - 5 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1930 May 20 (Box 7)
        - 1933 November 15 (Box 13)
        - 1934 September 14 (Box 15)
        - 1935 July 29 (Box 17)
        - 1936 September 26 (Box 19)
    - Owen, Robert Lathan (1856-1947). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1937 January 8 (Box 20)
    - Pareto, Vilfredo Frederico Damaso (1848-1923)
      - 12 ALS to James Harvey Rogers, Celigny, Switzerland
        - 1915 October 22 (Box 1)
        - 1915 December 14 (Box 1)
        - 1916 February 9 (Box 1)
        - 1916 April 7 (Box 1)
        - 1916 December 12 (Box 1)
        - 1917 March 28 (Box 1)
        - 1917 March 30 (Box 1)
        - 1919 October 28 (Box 1)
        - 1920 January 10 (Box 1)
        - 1920 February 11 (Box 1)
        - 1921 August 17 (Box 1)
        - 1921 December 31 (Box 1)
    - Pearson, Frank Ashmore (1887-)
      - 8 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Ithaca, N.Y.
        - 1923 March 27 (Box 2)
        - 1928 October 29 (Box 5)
        - 1928 November 9 (Box 5)
        - 1929 May 1 (Box 6)
        - 1933 July 29 (Box 12)
        - 1935 July 12 (Box 17)
    - Persons, Warren Milton (1878-1937). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York, 1934 May 9 (Box 14)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, Pres. U.S. (1882-1945)
      - 4 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1935 September 28 (Box 17)
        - 1935 December 3 (Box 17)
        - 1936 September 8 (Box 19)
        - 1936 December 10 (Box 20)
    - Roosevelt, James (1907-). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1937 November 8 (Box 21)
    - Roper, Daniel Calhoun (1867-1943)
      - 12 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1932 January 8 (Box 9)
        - 1933 September 20 (Box 12)
        - 1933 September 22 (Box 12)
        - 1933 September 28 (Box 12)
        - 1933 December 1 (Box 13)
        - 1933 December 10 (Box 13)
        - 1934 January 8 (Box 13)
        - 1934 February 9 (Box 13)
        - 1936 February 3 (Box 18)
        - 1936 November 9 (Box 19)
        - 1939 April 28 (Box 24)
        - 1939 May 6 (Box 24)
    - Rorty, Malcolm Churchill (1875-1936)
      - 6 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1922 December 12 (Box 2)
        - 1923 February 8 (Box 2)
        - 1923 March 9 (Box 2)
        - 1930 March 12 (Box 7)
        - 1933 September 23 (Box 12)
        - 1934 January 2 (Box 13)
    - Rostow, Walt Whitman (1916-)
      - 6 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1936 August 31 (Box 19)
        - 1936 December undated (Box 19–20)
        - 1937 April 15 (Box 20)
        - 1937 April 23 (Box 20)
        - 1937 April undated (Box 20)
        - 1937 September undated (Box 21)
    - Salter, Sir James Arthur (1881-). ALS to James Harvey Rogers, London, 1933 September 5 (Box 12)
    - Sellin, Johan Thorsten (1896-)
      - 5 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Philadelphia
        - 1930 April 5 (Box 7)
        - 1930 April 14 (Box 7)
        - 1930 April 19 (Box 7)
        - 1930 April 28 (Box 7)
        - 1930 May 15 (Box 7)
    - Shriver, Robert Sargent (1915-). 24 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York, 1934-1939 (Box 13–24)
    - Slichter, Sumner Huber (1892-1959)
      - 14 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1924 April 10 (Box 2)
        - 1924 November 14 (Box 2)
        - 1925 May 12 (Box 3)
        - 1925 August 24 (Box 3)
        - 1926 May 28 (Box 3)
        - 1927 February 21 (Box 4)
        - 1927 March 21 (Box 4)
        - 1927 March 30 (Box 4)
        - 1929 April 23 (Box 6)
        - 1938 May 28 (Box 22)
        - 1939 January 27 (2) (Box 23)
        - 1939 February 9 (Box 24)
        - 1939 February 12 (Box 24)
    - Smoot, Reed (1862-1941)
      - 3 TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1933 February 8 (Box 11)
        - 1933 February 24 (Box 11)
        - 1933 February 25 (Box 11)
    - Strakosch, Sir Henry (1886-1939)
      - 5 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1933 September 11 (Box 12)
        - 1933 December 11 (Box 13)
        - 1935 June 4 (Box 16)
        - 1936 September 4 (Box 19)
        - 1936 November 25 (Box 19)
    - Streit, Samuel Frederick (1870-)
      - 6 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
        - 1924 March 10 (Box 2)
        - 1924 March 25 (Box 2)
        - 1925 January 29 (Box 3)
        - 1926 February 11 (Box 3)
        - 1926 May 18 (Box 3)
        - 1927 February 1 (Box 4)
    - Strong, James George (1870-1938). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1926 July 20 (Box 3)
    - Taussig, Frank William (1859-1940)
      - 13 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Cambridge, Mass.
        - 1925 April 15 (Box 3)
        - 1925 October 20 (Box 3)
        - 1926 February 25 (Box 3)
        - 1926 March 9 (Box 3)
        - 1926 March 15 (Box 3)
        - 1926 March 25 (Box 3)
        - 1926 April 1 (Box 3)
        - 1926 April 20 (Box 3)
        - 1926 April 29 (Box 3)
        - 1926 May 11 (Box 3)
        - 1927 March 1 (Box 4)
        - 1933 February 8 (Box 11)
        - 1933 February 16 (Box 11)
    - Thomas, Elmer (1876-)
      - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1933 January 30 (Box 11)
        - 1933 February 11 (Box 11)
    - Thruston, Elliott Ladd (1895-)
      - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1937 January 9 (Box 20)
        - 1937 January 23 (Box 20)
    - Tinkham, George Holden (1870-). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1938 February 5 (Box 22)
    - Tunney, Gene (1898-). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York, 1934 December 21 (Box 16)
    - Viner, Jacob (1892-)
      - 8 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1928 October 15 (Box 5)
        - 1929 April 16 (Box 6)
        - 1930 February 24 (Box 7)
        - 1931 December 7 (Box 9)
        - 1933 February 17 (Box 11)
        - 1933 September 13 (2) (Box 12)
        - 1934 October 29 (Box 15)
        - 1 undated (Box 24)
    - Wallace, Henry Agard (1888-)
      - 5 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1928 August 21 (Box 5)
        - 1931 November 24 (Box 9)
        - 1935 March 8 (Box 16)
        - 1935 November 29 (Box 17)
        - 1935 December 18 (Box 17)
    - Warren, George Frederick (1874-1938)
      - 6 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1933 August 3 (Box 12)
        - 1933 September 21 (Box 12)
        - 1933 September 25 (Box 12)
        - 1934 January 3 (Box 13)
        - 1935 April 13 (Box 16)
        - 1935 July 2 (Box 17)
    - Zimmern, Alfred (1879-1957)
      - 2 ALS to James Harvey Rogers
        - 1933 November 3, Toronto, Canada (Box 13)
        - 1934 February 14, Oxford, England (Box 13)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, Pres. U.S. (1882-1945)
    - 4 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1935 September 28 (Box 17)
      - 1935 December 3 (Box 17)
      - 1936 September 8 (Box 19)
      - 1936 December 10 (Box 20)
    - 17 TL copies written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1925 October 14 (Box 3)
      - 1933 July 21 (Box 12)
      - 1933 July 24 (Box 12)
      - 1933 August 31 (Box 12)
      - 1933 October 20 (Box 12)
      - 1933 December 9 (Box 13)
      - 1935 May 17 (Box 16)
      - 1935 June 3 (Box 16)
      - 1935 September 17 (Box 17)
      - 1935 November 26 (Box 17)
      - 1936 August 26 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 10 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 17 (Box 19)
      - 1937 July 28 (Box 21)
      - 1937 October 8 (Box 21)
      - 1938 December 14 (Box 21)
      - 1939 January 27 (Box 23)
      - Letters for these dates were enclosed with letters to Marvin Hunter McIntyre:
        - 1935 May 17 (Box 16)
        - 1935 June 3 (Box 16)
        - 1935 November 26 (Box 17)
        - 1936 August 26 (Box 19)
        - 1936 November 10 (Box 19)
        - 1936 November 17 (Box 19)
        - 1937 July 28 (Box 21)
        - 1937 October 8 (Box 21)
        - 1938 December 14 (Box 21)
        - 1939 January 27 (Box 23)
  - Roosevelt, James (1907-). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1937 November 8 (Box 21)
  - Roper, Daniel Calhoun (1867-1943)
    - 12 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1932 January 8 (Box 9)
      - 1933 September 20 (Box 12)
      - 1933 September 22 (Box 12)
      - 1933 September 28 (Box 12)
      - 1933 December 1 (Box 13)
      - 1933 December 10 (Box 13)
      - 1934 January 8 (Box 13)
      - 1934 February 9 (Box 13)
      - 1936 February 3 (Box 18)
      - 1936 November 9 (Box 19)
      - 1939 April 28 (Box 24)
      - 1939 May 6 (Box 24)
    - 17 TL (copies) and telegram written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1932 January 11 (Box 9)
      - 1933 August 2 (Box 12)
      - 1933 September 2 (Box 12)
      - 1933 September 19 (Box 12)
      - 1933 October 20 (Box 12)
      - 1934 February 8 (Box 13)
      - 1934 March 20 (Box 14)
      - 1934 September 11 (Box 15)
      - 1934 September 12 (Box 15)
      - 1935 November 27 (Box 17)
      - 1936 January 15 (Box 17)
      - 1936 January 30 (Box 17)
      - 1936 February 14 (Box 18)
      - 1936 September 25 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 3 (Box 19)
      - 1939 April 30 (Box 24)
      - 1939 May 28 (Box 24)
  - Rorty, Malcolm Churchill (1875-1936)
    - 6 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1922 December 12 (Box 2)
      - 1923 February 8 (Box 2)
      - 1923 March 9 (Box 2)
      - 1930 March 12 (Box 7)
      - 1933 September 23 (Box 12)
      - 1934 January 2 (Box 13)
    - TL (copy) written by George Frederick Warren (1874-1938), Washington, D.C., 1934 January 8 (Box 13)
  - Rostow, Eugene Victor (1913-)
    - 15 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1933 [November 11] (Box 13)
      - 1936 July 14 (Box 19)
      - 1936 [Aug] undated (Box 19)
      - 1937 March 3 (Box 20)
      - 1938 March 19 (Box 22)
      - 1938 May 13 (Box 22)
      - 1939 June 2 (Box 23)
      - 8 undated (Box 24)
    - TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1933 December 21 (Box 13)
  - Rostow, Walt Whitman (1916-)
    - 6 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1936 August 31 (Box 19)
      - 1936 December undated (Box 19–20)
      - 1937 April 15 (Box 20)
      - 1937 April 23 (Box 20)
      - 1937 April undated (Box 20)
      - 1937 September undated (Box 21)
  - Salter, Sir James Arthur (1881-). ALS to James Harvey Rogers, London, 1933 September 5 (Box 12)
  - Sellin, Johan Thorsten (1896-)
    - 5 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Philadelphia
      - 1930 April 5 (Box 7)
      - 1930 April 14 (Box 7)
      - 1930 April 19 (Box 7)
      - 1930 April 28 (Box 7)
      - 1930 May 15 (Box 7)
  - Shriver, Robert Sargent (1915-)
    - 24 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York (Box 7)
    - 2 TLS written by S. Randolph Noble (1887-), Montreal
      - 1937 April 21 (Box 20)
      - 1938 October 18 (Box 23)
  - Sinclair, Upton Beall (1878-). TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, no place, 1922 October 12 (Box 1)
  - Slichter, Sumner Huber (1892-1959)
    - 14 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1924 April 10 (Box 2)
      - 1924 November 14 (Box 2)
      - 1925 May 12 (Box 3)
      - 1925 August 24 (Box 3)
      - 1926 May 28 (Box 3)
      - 1927 February 21 (Box 4)
      - 1927 March 21 (Box 4)
      - 1927 March 30 (Box 4)
      - 1929 April 23 (Box 6)
      - 1938 May 28 (Box 22)
      - 1939 January 27 (2) (Box 23)
      - 1939 February 9 (Box 24)
      - 1939 February 12 (Box 24)
    - 17 TL copies written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1924 June 7 (Box 2)
      - 1924 September 25 (Box 2)
      - 1924 November 11 (Box 2)
      - 1925 May 8 (Box 3)
      - 1926 February 20 (Box 3)
      - 1926 June 7 (Box 3)
      - 1927 March 2 (Box 4)
      - 1927 March 9 (Box 4)
      - 1927 March 26 (Box 4)
      - 1929 April 22 (Box 6)
      - 1932 May 17 (Box 10)
      - 1932 May 21 (Box 10)
      - 1937 March 12 (Box 20)
      - 1938 June 2 (Box 22)
      - 1939 January 18 (Box 23)
      - 1939 January 25 (Box 23)
      - 1939 February 10 (Box 24)
  - Smoot, Reed (1862-1941)
    - 3 TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1933 February 8 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 24 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 25 (Box 11)
  - Snyder, Carl (1869-1946)
    - 91 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1922 April 24 (Box 1)
      - 1922 May 1 (Box 1)
      - 1922 May 6 (Box 1)
      - 1922 May 15 (Box 1)
      - 1922 May 26 (Box 1)
      - 1922 November 21 (Box 2)
      - 1922 December 12 (Box 2)
      - 1923 February 9 (Box 2)
      - 1923 April 30 (Box 2)
      - 1923 May 14 (Box 2)
      - 1923 May 16 (Box 2)
      - 1923 December 11 (Box 2)
      - 1924 February 6 (Box 2)
      - 1924 March 6 (Box 2)
      - 1924 March 24 (Box 2)
      - 1925 February 17 (Box 3)
      - 1925 December 22 (Box 3)
      - 1926 February 10 (Box 3)
      - 1926 March 24 (Box 3)
      - 1926 April 22 (Box 3)
      - 1927 February 24 (Box 4)
      - 1927 March 1 (Box 4)
      - 1927 March 25 (Box 4)
      - 1928 March 8 (Box 5)
      - 1928 April 12 (Box 5)
      - 1928 October 16 (Box 5)
      - 1928 October 30 (Box 5)
      - 1928 November 2 (Box 5)
      - 1928 November 11 (Box 5)
      - 1929 February 14 (Box 6)
      - 1929 November 12 (Box 6)
      - 1929 December 18 (Box 6)
      - 1930 January 14 (2) (Box 7)
      - 1930 March 5 (Box 7)
      - 1930 March 18 (Box 7)
      - 1930 May 16 (Box 7)
      - 1930 June 2 (Box 7)
      - 1930 October 9 (Box 7)
      - 1930 December 16 (Box 8)
      - 1931 February 20 (Box 8)
      - 1931 March 2 (Box 8)
      - 1931 March 6 (Box 8)
      - 1931 March 9 (Box 8)
      - 1931 May 4 (Box 8)
      - 1931 May 27 (Box 8)
      - 1931 June 5 (Box 8)
      - 1931 July 10 (Box 8)
      - 1931 July 17 (Box 8)
      - 1931 September 10 (Box 8)
      - 1931 October 17 (Box 9)
      - 1931 October 28 (2) (Box 9)
      - 1931 December 23 (Box 9)
      - 1932 January 18 (Box 9)
      - 1932 March 1 (Box 10)
      - 1932 April 25 (Box 10)
      - 1932 April 28 (Box 10)
      - 1932 May 10 (Box 10)
      - 1932 July 12 (Box 10)
      - 1932 July 15 (Box 10)
      - 1932 November 25 (Box 11)
      - 1932 December 8 (Box 11)
      - 1933 January 3 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 7 (Box 11)
      - 1933 March 13 (Box 11)
      - 1933 April 24 (Box 11)
      - 1933 August 8 (Box 12)
      - 1934 March 16 (Box 13)
      - 1934 October 15 (Box 15)
      - 1934 December 20 (Box 16)
      - 1935 January 16 (Box 16)
      - 1935 March 13 (Box 16)
      - 1935 March 19 (Box 16)
      - 1935 July 26 (Box 17)
      - 1935 November [11] (Box 17)
      - 1936 March 30 (Box 18)
      - 1936 August 20 (Box 19)
      - 1936 October 21 (Box 19)
      - 1937 April 16 (Box 20)
      - 1937 July 16 (Box 21)
      - 1937 July 28 (Box 21)
      - 1937 November [2] (Box 21)
      - 1937 November 3 (Box 21)
      - 1938 July 20 (Box 22)
      - 1938 July 22 (Box 22)
      - 1938 August 18 (Box 22)
      - 1938 November 15 (Box 23)
      - 4 ALS undated (Box 24)
  - Strakosch, Sir Henry (1871-1943)
    - 5 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1933 September 11 (Box 12)
      - 1933 December 11 (Box 13)
      - 1935 June 4 (Box 16)
      - 1936 September 4 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 25 (Box 19)
    - 6 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1933 September 15 (Box 12)
      - 1935 May 24 (Box 16)
      - 1935 June 5 (Box 16)
      - 1936 August 27 (Box 19)
      - 1936 December 7 (Box 20)
      - 1938 June 8 (Box 22)
  - Streit, Samuel Frederick (1870-)
    - 6 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
      - 1924 March 10 (Box 2)
      - 1924 March 25 (Box 2)
      - 1925 January 29 (Box 3)
      - 1926 February 11 (Box 3)
      - 1926 May 18 (Box 3)
      - 1927 February 1 (Box 4)
  - Strong, Benjamin (1872-1928). TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, no place, 1926 July 19 (Box 3)
  - Taussig, Frank William (1859-1940)
    - 13 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Cambridge, Mass.
      - 1925 April 15 (Box 3)
      - 1925 October 20 (Box 3)
      - 1926 February 25 (Box 3)
      - 1926 March 9 (Box 3)
      - 1926 March 15 (Box 3)
      - 1926 March 25 (Box 3)
      - 1926 April 1 (Box 3)
      - 1926 April 20 (Box 3)
      - 1926 April 29 (Box 3)
      - 1926 May 11 (Box 3)
      - 1927 March 1 (Box 4)
      - 1933 February 8 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 16 (Box 11)
    - 12 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1925 January 13 (Box 3)
      - 1925 October 14 (Box 3)
      - 1925 October 30 (Box 3)
      - 1926 March 4 (Box 3)
      - 1926 March 13 (Box 3)
      - 1926 March 20 (Box 3)
      - 1926 March 17 (Box 3)
      - 1926 April 14 (Box 3)
      - 1926 April 24 (Box 3)
      - 1926 May 7 (Box 3)
      - 1927 February 24 (Box 4)
      - 1933 February 13 (Box 11)
  - Thomas, Elmer (1876-)
    - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1933 January 30 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 11 (Box 11)
    - TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, New Haven, 1933 February 6 (Box 11)
  - Thruston, Elliott Ladd (1895-)
    - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1937 January 9 (Box 20)
      - 1937 January 23 (Box 20)
  - Tinkham, George Holden (1870-1956)
    - TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1938 February 5 (Box 22)
    - TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, New Haven, 1938 February 11 (Box 22)
  - Tugwell, Rexford Guy (1891-)
    - 3 TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1932 November 3 (Box 11)
      - 1932 November 19 (Box 11)
      - 1935 May 25 (Box 16)
  - Tunney, Gene (1898-). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York, 1934 December 21 (Box 16)
  - Viner, Jacob (1892-)
    - 8 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1928 October 15 (Box 5)
      - 1929 April 16 (Box 6)
      - 1930 February 24 (Box 7)
      - 1931 December 7 (Box 9)
      - 1933 February 17 (Box 11)
      - 1933 September 13 (2) (Box 12)
      - 1934 October 29 (Box 15)
      - 1 undated (Box 24)
    - Telegram written by James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1933 November 10 (Box 13)
  - Wallace, Henry Agard (1888-)
    - 5 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1928 August 21 (Box 5)
      - 1931 November 24 (Box 9)
      - 1935 March 8 (Box 16)
      - 1935 November 29 (Box 17)
      - 1935 December 18 (Box 17)
    - 9 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1928 September 22 (Box 5)
      - 1931 December 4 (Box 9)
      - 1933 September 2 (Box 12)
      - 1934 March 20 (Box 14)
      - 1935 February 12 (Box 16)
      - 1935 June 3 (Box 16)
      - 1935 December 3 (Box 17)
      - 1935 December 4 (Box 17)
      - 1936 November 3 (Box 19)
    - TL (copy) written by George Frederick Warren, Washington, D.C., 1933 November 28 (Box 13)
  - Warburg, James Paul (1896-)
    - 2 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, no place
      - 1933 May 2 (Box 11)
      - 1 undated (Box 24)
  - Warren, George Frederick (1874-1938)
    - 6 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1933 August 3 (Box 12)
      - 1933 September 21 (Box 12)
      - 1933 September 25 (Box 12)
      - 1934 January 3 (Box 13)
      - 1935 April 13 (Box 16)
      - 1935 July 2 (Box 17)
    - 13 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1932 March 8 (Box 10)
      - 1932 March 26 (Box 10)
      - 1933 August 1 (2) (Box 12)
      - 1933 August 2 (Box 12)
      - 1933 August 3 (Box 12)
      - 1933 August 8 (Box 12)
      - 1933 October 30 (Box 13)
      - 1933 November 1 (Box 13)
      - 1934 January 23 (Box 13)
      - 1934 October 19 (Box 15)
      - 1935 June 7 (Box 16)
      - 1935 June 21 (Box 16)
    - TL (copy) to Henry Bruere, Washington, D.C., 1933 November 8 (Box 13)
    - TL (copy) to Marvin Hunter McIntyre, Washington, D.C., 1933 November 13 (Box 13)
    - TL (copy) to Henry Morgenthau, Washington, D.C., 1934 February 7 (Box 13)
    - TL (copy) to Herman Oliphant, Washington, D.C., 1934 February 1 (Box 13)
    - 2 telegrams to Frank Ashmore Pearson, Washington, D.C., 1933 November 7 (2) (Box 13)
    - TL (copy) to Malcolm Churchill Rorty, Washington, D.C., 1934 January 8 (Box 13)
    - TL (copy) to Henry Agard Wallace, Washington, D.C., 1933 November 28 (Box 13)